puredef.com 2014-05-22

# Puredef.com - Get song lyrics, music downloads, and more!

## Our Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 
  * To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) 

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that sites and service providers may transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser. They enable the site and service provider systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. You can turn off cookies in your settings at any time.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or other's rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Opt-Out**

We currently do not send messages to or collect data from users. If at any time we do contact you, it would only be for support reasons. If in that regard, you would like stop receiving messages or notifications, you can click on an unsubscribe link from any message we provide to no longer receive our messages.

If you would like to be removed from our system, you can contact us at: [support@puredef.com](mailto:support@puredef.com).

**How Do Toolbars Affect Your Browser And Operating System?**

Toolbars install into your Internet browser and allow you to search the Internet. If you consent to make a toolbar your default search, your Internet browser default search feature will be set and you will access search services (i) by entering queries in your browser search box; (ii) by entering queries in your browser address bar, and/or (iii) in response to misspelled, incorrectly formatted or unresolved DNS submissions in your browser address bar.

Toolbars do not affect your operating system. Toolbars can be removed at any time. For more information regarding toolbars, visit <http://support.search.us.com/license.php>.

If you would like to reset your browser, follow the General Toolbar Instructions below.

**General Toolbar Uninstall Instructions:**

If, for any reason at all, you decide you no longer want the downloaded software or offers on your computer, you can easily uninstall them at any time. We’re sorry to see you go!

The following are general instructions regarding the software uninstallation process:

**For Firefox Users**  
(Internet Explorer & Chrome users: please follow the instructions “For Windows Users” below).

  * Go to the orange “Firefox” menu located at the top left of your Firefox browser window
  * Select “Add-ons” to open the Add-ons Manager
  * Under “Extensions” click the name of the add-on that you would like to disable or remove
  * Select “Disable” or “Remove”
  * Select the “Restart Now” link to restart Firefox

That’s it! You will now have successfully uninstalled the software.

**For Windows 7 and Vista Users**

  * Go to the ”Start Menu” located at the bottom right of your screen
  * Select ”Control Panel”
  * Under ”Programs” click “Uninstall a Program”
  * Right click on the program you wish to remove, then click ”Uninstall/Change“
  * Follow the uninstallation steps

That’s it! You will now have successfully uninstalled the software.

**For Windows XP Users**

  * Go to the ”Start Menu” located at the bottom right of your screen
  * Select ”Control Panel”
  * Click “Add or Remove Programs“
  * Click the program you wish to remove, then click “Remove” or “Change/Remove“
  * Follow the uninstallation steps

That’s it! You will now have successfully uninstalled the software.

**For Windows 95, 98, Me, NT, 2000, and XP Users In Classic View**

  * From the "Start Menu," select "Settings," and then "Control Panel"
  * Double-click the “Add/Remove Programs” icon
  * Select the program you wish to remove and click on the “Remove” or “Change/Remove” button
  * Follow the prompts to finish the uninstallation of the software

That’s it! You will now have successfully uninstalled the software.

*Note: After you have uninstalled the software, certain data such as folders, files, registry keys, and cookies, may remain on your computer. We recommend that you clear your cookies after uninstalling.

**If for any reason you are having difficulties uninstalling your software, please email us at [support@puredef.com](mailto:support@puredef.com).

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account via the "Sign In" link on the top right of the home page. Then click on 'Page Settings' and then go to the 'Account' section.

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act). We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our "Terms and Conditions" section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at: http://www.puredef.com/terms.html

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy was last modified **June, 15 2012.**

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions, comments or recommendations about Toolbars, please visit <http://support.search.us.com/about.php>

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

PureDEF.com  
425 Bush Street  
San Francisco, CA 94108  
USA
